<resources>
    <string name="app_name">A9Dex</string>
    <string name="abbmod_app_id"></string>
    <string name="admob_main"></string>
    <string name="admin_details"></string>
    <string name="chartlic" translatable="false">Copyright 2016 Philipp Jahoda\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\"); you may not use this file except in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="trco" translatable="false">All product names and images shown or represented are copyright and/or trademark of theirs respective copyright and/or trademark holders, which are in no way associated or affiliated with this application. Use of these names does not imply any co-operation or endorsement.\n\nThis app is developed and designed for educational purpose.</string>
    <string name="glide_lic" translatable="false">License for everything not in third_party and not otherwise marked:\n\nCopyright 2014 Google, Inc. All rights reserved.\n\nRedistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are\npermitted provided that the following conditions are met:\n\n   1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of\n         conditions and the following disclaimer.\n\n   2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list\n         of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials\n         provided with the distribution.\n\nTHIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY GOOGLE, INC. ``AS IS\'\' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED\nWARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND\nFITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL GOOGLE, INC. OR\nCONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR\nCONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR\nSERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON\nANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING\nNEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF\nADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.\n\nThe views and conclusions contained in the software and documentation are those of the\nauthors and should not be interpreted as representing official policies, either expressed\nor implied, of Google, Inc.\n---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\nLicense for third_party/disklrucache:\n\nCopyright 2012 Jake Wharton\nCopyright 2011 The Android Open Source Project\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the \"License\");\nyou may not use this file except in compliance with the License.\nYou may obtain a copy of the License at\n\n   http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software\ndistributed under the License is distributed on an \"AS IS\" BASIS,\nWITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.\nSee the License for the specific language governing permissions and\nlimitations under the License.\n---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\nLicense for third_party/gif_decoder:\n\nCopyright © 2013 Xcellent Creations, Inc.\n\nPermission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining\na copy of this software and associated documentation files (the\n\"Software\"), to deal in the Software without restriction, including\nwithout limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish,\ndistribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to\npermit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to\nthe following conditions:\n\nThe above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be\nincluded in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.\n\nTHE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,\nEXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF\nMERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND\nNONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE\nLIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION\nOF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION\nWITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.\n---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------\nLicense for third_party/gif_encoder/AnimatedGifEncoder.java and\nthird_party/gif_encoder/LZWEncoder.java:\n\nNo copyright asserted on the source code of this class. May be used for any\npurpose, however, refer to the Unisys LZW patent for restrictions on use of\nthe associated LZWEncoder class. Please forward any corrections to\nkweiner@fmsware.com.\n\n-----------------------------------------------------------------------------\nLicense for third_party/gif_encoder/NeuQuant.java\n\nCopyright © 1994 Anthony Dekker\n\nNEUQUANT Neural-Net quantization algorithm by Anthony Dekker, 1994. See\n\"Kohonen neural networks for optimal colour quantization\" in \"Network:\nComputation in Neural Systems\" Vol. 5 (1994) pp 351-367. for a discussion of\nthe algorithm.\n\nAny party obtaining a copy of these files from the author, directly or\nindirectly, is granted, free of charge, a full and unrestricted irrevocable,\nworld-wide, paid up, royalty-free, nonexclusive right and license to deal in\nthis software and documentation files (the \"Software\"), including without\nlimitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute,\nsublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons who\nreceive copies from any such party to do so, with the only requirement being\nthat this copyright notice remain intact.</string>
    <string name="apache" translatable="false">Copyright © 2007-2018, The Android Open Source Project\n\nLicensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at\n\nhttp://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
\n\nUnless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.</string>
    <string name="stickygrid" translatable="false">The MIT License (MIT)\n\n

Copyright (c) 2017 Sergej Kravcenko\n\n

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:
\n\n
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all
copies or substantial portions of the Software.
\n\n
THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE
SOFTWARE.</string>
    <string name="newwebview" translatable="false">Copyright 2017 Sira Lam\n\n

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and
associated documentation files (the WebViewSuite), to deal in the Software without restriction,
including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense,
and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so,
subject to the following conditions:\n\n

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or
substantial portions of the Software.\n\n

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED,
INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM,
DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</string>

    <string name="fontlicence" translatable="false">
        RAJDHANI FONT\n\n
        PREAMBLE\n\n
The goals of the Open Font License (OFL) are to stimulate worldwide
development of collaborative font projects, to support the font creation
efforts of academic and linguistic communities, and to provide a free and
open framework in which fonts may be shared and improved in partnership
with others.\n\n

The OFL allows the licensed fonts to be used, studied, modified and
redistributed freely as long as they are not sold by themselves. The
fonts, including any derivative works, can be bundled, embedded,
redistributed and/or sold with any software provided that any reserved
names are not used by derivative works. The fonts and derivatives,
however, cannot be released under any other type of license. The
requirement for fonts to remain under this license does not apply
to any document created using the fonts or their derivatives.\n\n

DEFINITIONS\n
"Font Software" refers to the set of files released by the Copyright
Holder(s) under this license and clearly marked as such. This may
include source files, build scripts and documentation.\n\n

"Reserved Font Name" refers to any names specified as such after the
copyright statement(s).\n\n

"Original Version" refers to the collection of Font Software components as
distributed by the Copyright Holder(s).\n\n

"Modified Version" refers to any derivative made by adding to, deleting,
or substituting — in part or in whole — any of the components of the
Original Version, by changing formats or by porting the Font Software to a
new environment.\n\n

"Author" refers to any designer, engineer, programmer, technical
writer or other person who contributed to the Font Software.

PERMISSION and CONDITIONS\n
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining
a copy of the Font Software, to use, study, copy, merge, embed, modify,
redistribute, and sell modified and unmodified copies of the Font
Software, subject to the following conditions:\n\n

1) Neither the Font Software nor any of its individual components,
in Original or Modified Versions, may be sold by itself.\n\n

2) Original or Modified Versions of the Font Software may be bundled,
redistributed and/or sold with any software, provided that each copy
contains the above copyright notice and this license. These can be
included either as stand-alone text files, human-readable headers or
in the appropriate machine-readable metadata fields within text or
binary files as long as those fields can be easily viewed by the user.\n\n

3) No Modified Version of the Font Software may use the Reserved Font
Name(s) unless explicit written permission is granted by the corresponding
Copyright Holder. This restriction only applies to the primary font name as
presented to the users.\n\n

4) The name(s) of the Copyright Holder(s) or the Author(s) of the Font
Software shall not be used to promote, endorse or advertise any
Modified Version, except to acknowledge the contribution(s) of the
Copyright Holder(s) and the Author(s) or with their explicit written
permission.\n\n

5) The Font Software, modified or unmodified, in part or in whole,
must be distributed entirely under this license, and must not be
distributed under any other license. The requirement for fonts to
remain under this license does not apply to any document created
using the Font Software.\n\n

TERMINATION\n
This license becomes null and void if any of the above conditions are
not met.\n\n

DISCLAIMER\n
THE FONT SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES OF
MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT
OF COPYRIGHT, PATENT, TRADEMARK, OR OTHER RIGHT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
COPYRIGHT HOLDER BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY,
INCLUDING ANY GENERAL, SPECIAL, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL
DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING
FROM, OUT OF THE USE OR INABILITY TO USE THE FONT SOFTWARE OR FROM
OTHER DEALINGS IN THE FONT SOFTWARE.</string>
    <string name="cars">Cars</string>
    <string name="test_id"></string>
    <string name="route">Fastest Route</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="dev_design" translatable="false">Developer and Designer</string>
    <string name="dev_name" translatable="false">Manas Mahajan</string>
    <string name="dev_cmpny" translatable="false">Adnyey</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="mail_id" translatable="false">adnyey.mail@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="notif_exit">Press again to exit</string>
    <string name="patron">Become a Patron</string>
    <string name="filled_bullet">\u25CF</string>
</resources>
